job-q.com 2010-04-30

# 

|  |  Privacy Policy of Job-Q.com   
|  Privacy Policy  
---  
  
Privacy Policy Statement

Job-Q.com ("WEBSITE") takes privacy very seriously. 

  1. We collect personal information in this WEBSITE. Job-Q.com owns the information submitted, however, we are committed not to disclose any personal information to any third party without consent of USERS (i.e., job seeker and employer)  
Exceptions to this clause are:  
\- If it is required by law, e.g., by court order   
\- In the event of transfer of ownership of the WEBSITE as a whole 
  2. We may use the collected information for our internal usage. Such usage will be limited only for statistical study to improve our services in the WEBSITE 
  3. To protect privacy of both companies and job seekers, we provide option to hide profile information that is submitted to the site (public viewing disabled)
  4. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to·not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html). 

Job-Q.com responsibilities and liabilities in safeguarding this privacy policy is stated in Terms and Conditions  
  
|  | **   Member Login**  
---  
  
**Username**

|   
  
**Password**

|   
**Login As** |  Job Seekers   
  |  Employers  

| **   Site Statistics **  
---  
  | Users Online |  66   
  | Job-seekers |  67686   
  | Employers  |  4579   
  | Jobs |  5118   
  |  Resumes |  28289   
  |  Companies |  1935   
   
| **    Advertisements **  
---
